Viewers all over the world, where can you go from His Spirit?
The Spirit of God is everywhere.
I say, I release you in the name of Jesus!
Are you oppressed?
Be free!
Are you sick?
Be healed!
Are you poor?
Be blessed!
Be free!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua, touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Once again...viewers you are under the sound of this voice
The voice of God says, "Are you weak?"
Be strong.
The voice of God say, "Are you sick?"
Be healed!
The voice of God says, "are you poor?"
Be blessed!
The voice of God says, "are you oppressed?"
Be free!
Say, "I am free!"
"I am healed!."
"I am delivered!"
"I am free!"
"I am saved!"
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua; touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Viewers all over the world,
whatever bondage that you are in...
I release you in the name of Jesus!
Everyone who is under the influence of this voice...be released.
Be released!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua, touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Viewers all over the world,
listen to me. I say to you...be delivered!
Be delivered!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua, touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Every spirit-spirit of killing, stealing, destruction, I say be delivered!
I rescue you in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus.
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua, touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Viewers all over the world,
begin to confess your freedom!
Confess your freedom!
I confirm your freedom!
I believe your freedom!
I confirm your healing!
I believe in your healing!
I confirm your deliverance!
Confess your deliverance!
I confirm your blessing.
Confess your blessing.
Begin to confess your blessing!
I confirm your healing!
Confess your healing.
I confirm your freedom!
Confess your freedom!
In the name of Jesus.
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua, touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Open your lips, and begin to confess it.
Viewers all over the world, say "I am free in the name of Jesus."
Give thanks to him! Give thanks to Him... for your freedom
Viewers all over the world, confess this...
You are worthy, O Lord!
You rescued me...you saved me...
you delivered me and blessed me
You are worthy!
O, Lord, thank you Jesus Christ name, we pray
Hallelujah.
We leave you under the influence of the Holy Spirit
and pray to meet you there again.
Allow your heart to be deeply engaged with God as you send your testimonies to info@scoan.org
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies, deliverances, service and testimonies,
from the Synagogue Church Of All Nations
Emmanuel TV....changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world,